

CONTACT ME AT

- Bumi Pasar Kemis Indah,Blok E4 No. 7, Pasar Kemis Tangerang, Indonesia
- vikyyahya.id@gmail.com
- 0895368019831
- www.takcoding.com
- in www.linkedin.com/in/vikyyahya-4bb570159/

SKILLS

- •••• Java
- •••• Javascript
- •••• Kotlin
- •••• Php
- •••• Android Development (native)
- • • Mobile Development (react-native)

VIKY YAHYA

MOBILE DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm an enthusiastic, responsible and hard working IT person. I am able to work well both in a team environment. I am able to work well under preasure and adhere to strict deadline. I am Mobile Developer since 2019, having good knowledge about Android, strong in algorithm, data structure, object oriented programming.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mobile Developer (Part Time)

PT. Sinergi Digital Teknologi | Dec 2019 - present

• Development Mobile App (android and ios) at lenna.ai, using android native and react-native.

Fullstack Developer (Internship)

PT. Sinergi Digital Teknologi | Sep 2019 - Dec 2019

 Create a web-based auction system use Vue JS and Laravel

Fullstack Developer (Freelance)

Titan Infra Energy | Dec 2019 - May 2020

 Create web-based refueling management system use Laravel

Administrative Product(Freelance)

PT Diansurya Global | Jul 2018 - Jul 2019

 Create standard operating procedures and make reports on the results of production

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Universitas Muhammadiyah Tangerang

Bachelor Degree Informatics Enginering | Jul 2015 - Nov 2019

• GPA: 3.56

SMK N 1 TRUCUK

BA Product Design | Dec 2008 - Dec 2011